const game = [
	{
		
		questions: [
			{
				question:
					'Life can bring much pain. There are many ways to deal with this pain. Choose wisely.',
				options: ['1985', 'Intro(KOD)', 'ATM', 'Motiv8'],
				answer: 'Intro(KOD)',
			},
			{
				question:
					"One day y'all have to decide, who you gon' be, A scary nigga or a nigga that’s gon’ rule like me.",
				options: ['Window Pain', 'Foldin Clothes', 'Nice Watch', 'Fire Squad'],
				answer: 'Fire Squad',
			},
			{
				question:
					'I know that everything that glitters ain’t gold, I know the shit ain’t always good as it seems, But tell me till you get it how could you know?',
				options: ['A Tale of Two Citiez', 'Nice Watch', 'Change', 'Deja vu'],
				answer: 'A Tale of Two Citiez',
			},
			{
				question: 'But the only real change come from inside.',
				options: ['Change', 'St. Tropez', 'January 28th', 'Hello'],
				answer: 'Change',
			},
			{
				question: 'I try to find employment even if it’s wiping toilets',
				options: ['4 Your Eyez Only', 'Premeditated Murder', 'No Holding Me Back', 'Relaxation'],
				answer: '4 Your Eyez Only',
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question:
					'Just because yo’ dick can spray semen, it don’t mean that you ready to let go of yo’ childish ways',
				options: ['Middle Child', 'Lost Ones', 'Window Pain', 'Photograph'],
				answer: 'Window Pain',
			},
			{
				question:
					'One thing about the men that’s controlling the pen that write history, they always seem to white-out they sins',
				options: ['The One', 'Brackets', 'Premditate Murder', 'ATM'],
				answer: 'Brackets',
			},
			{
				question:
					'I’m controlling my mind, the days are warm the nights are cold, the lost is found, I’m found',
				options: ['1985', '4 Your Eyez Only', 'Brackets', 'ATM'],
				answer: 'Brackets',
			},
			{
				question: 'My heart is big, I want to give too much',
				options: ['Vilematic', 'The Cut off', 'Nice Watch', 'Home For The Holidays'],
				answer: 'The Cut Off',
			},
			{
				question: 'What’s done in the dark will always find a way to shine',
				options: ["Kevin's Heart", 'The Autograph', 'Is She Gon Pop', 'Everybody Gotta Die'],
				answer: "Kevin's Heart",
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question: "How 'bout you listen and never forget?",
				options: ['HIgher', 'KOD', 'Once an Addict', 'Lights Please'],
				answer: 'KOD',
			},
			{
				question:
					'At the bottom of the hourglass lies sand that represents the past in which all of my demons rest, I’m calling out for help',
				options: ['Intro(KOD)', 'Premeditated Murder', 'No Holding Me Back', 'Relaxation'],
				answer: 'Intro(KOD)',
			},
			{
				question:
					'One thing about the men that’s controlling the pen that write history, they always seem to white-out they sins',
				options: ['The One', 'Brackets', 'Premeditated Murder', 'ATM'],
				answer: 'Brackets',
			},
			{
				question:
					'You coulda bought a crib with all that bread that you done blew, I know you think this type of revenue is never endin’. But I wanna take a minute just to tell you that ain’t true',
				options: ['1985', 'Blow Up', 'Middle Child', 'Lights Please'],
				answer: '1985',
			},
			{
				question: 'Life is all about the evolution',
				options: ['I really mean it', 'Change', 'Serenede', 'Who Dat'],
				answer: 'Change',
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question: 'Time will tell who is on my side',
				options: ['Need You Bad', "She's Mine Part 1", "She's Mine Part 2", 'The Cut Off'],
				answer: 'The Cut Off',
			},
			{
				question: 'Every time you go to sleep you look like you in Heaven',
				options: ['G.O.M.D', "She's Mine Part 1", "She's Mine Part 1", 'No Role Modelz'],
				answer: "She's Mine Part 1",
			},
			{
				question: 'Fell in love through photograph, I don’t even know your name',
				options: ['Love Yourz', 'Power Trip', 'False Prophets', 'Photograph'],
				answer: 'Photograph',
			},
			{
				question: 'Love today’s gone digital And it’s messing with my health',
				options: ['Good Game', 'Obstacles', 'Photograph', 'Villematic'],
				answer: 'Photograph',
			},
			{
				question: 'Don’t wanna die, ’cause now you’re here And I just wanna be right by your side',
				options: ['High For Hours', 'Shook Ones', "She's Mine part 2", 'Song for the ville'],
				answer: "She's Mine part 2",
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question: 'My life is too crazy, no actor could play me”',
				options: ['Forbidden Fruit', 'Photograph', 'KOD', 'Work Out'],
				answer: 'KOD',
			},
			{
				question: 'But see I’m growing and getting stronger with every breath',
				options: ['Change', 'A Tale of 2 Citiez', 'Let Nas Down', 'Wet Dreamz'],
				answer: 'Change',
			},
			{
				question: 'And the strongest drug of them all',
				options: ['1985', 'ATM', 'G.O.M.D', 'KOD'],
				answer: 'KOD',
			},
			{
				question:
					'I’m searching and praying and hoping for something, I know I’m gon’ see it, I know that it’s coming',

				options: ['Work Out', 'Everybody Dies', 'Mo Money', 'For Whom the Bell Tolls'],
				answer: 'For Whom the Bell Tolls',
			},
			{
				question: 'I had to cut some people off ’cause they was using me',
				options: ['She Knows', 'Love Yourz', 'Power Trip', 'The Cut Off'],
				answer: 'The Cut Off',
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question:
					'If I fell in love with you before I ever even knew, I catch your eye then look away as if it never happened',
				options: ['Deja Vu', 'Higher', 'In the Morning', "Daddy's Little Girl"],
				answer: 'Deja Vu',
			},
			{
				question:
					'Rejection makes you defensive, So you protect your pride with your reflexes, But life is a game with no reset on the end',
				options: ['Hello', 'Immortal', 'For whom the Bell Tolls', 'Foldin Clothes'],
				answer: 'Hello',
			},
			{
				question:
					'I was a fool, spent all my time ducking school, ducking cops, Ducking rules, hugging blocks that don’t love you',

				options: ['Crooked Smile', '4 Your Eyez Only', 'ATale of 2 Citiez', 'Lost Ones'],
				answer: '4 Your Eyez Only',
			},
			{
				question: 'Every loser gotta win and every winner gotta lose someday',
				options: ['The cut off', 'Change', 'Middle Child', 'Deja Vu'],
				answer: 'Deja Vu',
			},
			{
				question: 'If practice made perfect, I’m practice’s baby',
				options: ['Motiv8', 'Lights Please', 'KOD', 'Apparently'],
				answer: 'KOD',
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question: 'What good is the bread when my niggaz is broke...',
				options: ['Mo Money', 'Rich Niggaz', 'Trouble', 'Middle Child'],
				answer: 'Middle Child',
			},
			{
				question: 'So ahead of my time even when I rhyme aboutmy future I be reminiscing',
				options: ['The One', 'Brackets', 'Let Nas Down', 'Fire Squad'],
				answer: 'Fire Squad',
			},
			{
				question: "We ain't picture perfect, but we worth the picture still",
				options: ['Wet Dreamz', 'January 28th', 'Crooked Smile', 'Adolescence'],
				answer: 'Crooked Smile',
			},
			{
				question:
					'I got smart, I got rich and I got bitches still. And they all look like my eyebrows: thick as hell.',
				options: ['Trouble', 'Work Out', 'Power Trip', 'Crooked Smile'],
				answer: 'Crooked Smile',
			},
			{
				question:
					'On the road to riches, listen, this is what you find, the good news is nigga you came a long way the bad news is nigga you went the wrong way.',
				options: ['Love Yourz', 'Adolescence', 'Fire Squad', 'Everybody Gotta Die'],
				answer: 'Love Yourz',
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question:
					'If the pressure get too much for me to take and I break, Play this tape for my daughter and let her know my life is on it',
				options: ['Dollar and A Dream III', '4 Your Eyez Only', 'Ville Mentality', 'Immortal'],
				answer: '4 Your Eyez Only',
			},
			{
				question: 'I flip my misfortune and grow me a fortune',
				options: ['The One', 'Foldin Clothes', 'Premditate Murder', 'ATM'],
				answer: 'Brackets',
			},
			{
				question:
					'My fears alleviate, my tears evaporate My faith don’t deviate, ideas don’t have a date',
				options: ['She Knows', 'Love Yourz', 'Apparently', 'Change'],
				answer: 'Change',
			},
			{
				question: 'Feels so right to let things go',
				options: ['False Prophet', 'Friends', "Can't Get Enough", 'Window Pain'],
				answer: 'Friends',
			},
			{
				question:
					'I understand this message is not the coolest to say, But if you down to try it I know of a better way - Meditate',
				options: ['Nothing Lasts Forever', "God's Gift", 'Cole World', 'Friends'],
				answer: 'Nothing Lasts Forever',
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question: 'I love it when you give me Head, Ihatte it when you give me Heaache',
				options: ['Work Out', 'Lost Ones', 'Window Pain', "Can't Get Enough"],
				answer: "Can't Get Enough",
			},
			{
				question: "Money in your Palm don't make you real",
				options: ['The One', 'Brackets', 'Middle Child', 'ATM'],
				answer: 'Middle Child',
			},
			{
				question: 'First things first, rest in peace Uncle Phil',
				options: ['1985', 'Mr. Nice Watch', 'In The Morning', 'No Role Modelz'],
				answer: 'No Role Modelz',
			},
			{
				question:
					'One thing about your demons they bound to catch up one day, I’d rather see you stand up and face them than run away',
				options: ['Friends', "God's Gift", 'Nice Watch', 'Home For The Holidays'],
				answer: 'Friends',
			},
			{
				question:
					'Sometimes I think pain is just a lack of understanding, If we could only understand it all, would we feel no pain? God must feel no pain',
				options: ['Once an Addict', 'The Autograph', 'Cole World', 'Is She Gon Pop'],
				answer: ' Once an Addict',
			},
		],
	},

	{
		questions: [
			{
				question: "It's beauty in the struggle nigga, ugliness in the success",
				options: ['Home For the Holidays', 'ATM', 'Love Yourz', 'The Autograph'],
				answer: 'Love Yourz',
			},
			{
				question: 'They let a brother steer a ship but never told him that the ship was sinking.',
				options: ['The One', 'Hello', 'St. Tropez', 'Be Free'],
				answer: 'Be Free',
			},
			{
				question:
					"Well this has gotta be the longest crush ever. If I ever get to fuck it'd be the longest bust ever.",
				options: ['Mr. Nice Watch', 'Adolescence', 'Power Trip', 'ATM'],
				answer: 'Power Trip',
			},
			{
				question:
					"You call it runnin', I call it escapin'. Start a new life in a foreign location. Similar to my niggas duckin' cases.",
				options: ['Ville Mentality', 'Love Yourz', 'NWork Out', 'Home For The Holidays'],
				answer: 'Ville Mentality',
			},
			{
				question: 'Niggas congratulate me. I just tell them God is good.',
				options: ['Unabomber', 'I Got It', 'Show Me Something', 'The Last Stretch'],
				answer: 'Show Me Something',
			},
		],
	},
];

export {game}